(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[0],{24:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/src_sounds_wrong.e55862ad.mp3"},256:function(e,t){},275:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var r=a(0),n=a.n(r),c=a(18),o=a.n(c),s=(a(63),a(1)),i=(a(65),a(12)),u=a(52),m=a.n(u),l=a(53),d=a.n(l),f=a(24),x=a.n(f);a(67);function w(e){var t=e.data,a=e.setStop,c=e.questionNumber,o=e.setQuestionNumber,u=(e.setEarned,Object(r.useState)(t[c-1])),l=Object(s.a)(u,2),f=l[0],w=l[1],b=Object(r.useState)(null),h=Object(s.a)(b,2),p=h[0],E=h[1],N=Object(r.useState)("answer"),v=Object(s.a)(N,2),y=v[0],O=v[1],j=Object(i.a)(m.a),S=Object(s.a)(j,1)[0],g=Object(i.a)(d.a),q=Object(s.a)(g,1)[0],I=Object(i.a)(x.a),C=Object(s.a)(I,1)[0];Object(r.useEffect)(function(){w(t[c-1])},[t,c]),Object(r.useEffect)(function(){S()},[S]);var L=function(e){E(e),O("answer active"),setTimeout(function(){O(e.correct?"answer correct":"answer wrong")},3e3),setTimeout(function(){e.correct?(q(),setTimeout(function(){o(function(e){return e+1}),E(null)},1e3)):(C(),setTimeout(function(){a(!0)},1e3))},6e3)};return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"trivia"},n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question"},f.question),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"answers"},n.a.createElement("div",{className:p==f.answers[0]?y:"answer",onClick:function(){return L(f.answers[0])}},f.answers[0].text),n.a.createElement("div",{className:p==f.answers[1]?y:"answer",onClick:function(){return L(f.answers[1])}},f.answers[1].text),n.a.createElement("div",{className:p==f.answers[2]?y:"answer",onClick:function(){return L(f.answers[2])}},f.answers[2].text),n.a.createElement("div",{className:p==f.answers[3]?y:"answer",onClick:function(){return L(f.answers[3])}},f.answers[3].text)))}function b(e){var t=e.setStop,a=e.questionNumber,n=Object(r.useState)(30),c=Object(s.a)(n,2),o=c[0],u=c[1],m=Object(i.a)(x.a),l=Object(s.a)(m,1)[0];return Object(r.useEffect)(function(){if(0===o)return l(),t(!0);var e=setInterval(function(){u(function(e){return e-1})},1e3);return function(){return clearInterval(e)}}),Object(r.useEffect)(function(){u(30)},[a]),o}function h(e){var t=e.setUserName,a=Object(r.useRef)();return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"start"},n.a.createElement("input",{placeholder:"Enter your name",className:"startInput",ref:a}),n.a.createElement("button",{className:"startButton",onClick:function(){a.current.value&&t(a.current.value)}},"Start"))}var p=function(){var e=Object(r.useState)(null),t=Object(s.a)(e,2),a=t[0],c=t[1],o=Object(r.useState)(1),i=Object(s.a)(o,2),u=i[0],m=i[1],l=Object(r.useState)(!1),d=Object(s.a)(l,2),f=d[0],x=d[1],p=Object(r.useState)("Rs. 0"),E=Object(s.a)(p,2),N=E[0],v=E[1],y=[{id:1,amount:1e3},{id:2,amount:2e3},{id:3,amount:5e3},{id:4,amount:1e4},{id:5,amount:2e4},{id:6,amount:4e4},{id:7,amount:8e4},{id:8,amount:16e4},{id:9,amount:32e4},{id:10,amount:64e4},{id:11,amount:125e4},{id:12,amount:25e5},{id:13,amount:5e6},{id:14,amount:1e7}].reverse();return Object(r.useEffect)(function(){u>1&&v(y.find(function(e){return e.id===u-1}).amount)},[y,u]),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"app"},a?n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement("div",{className:"main"},f||u>14?n.a.createElement("h1",{className:"endText"},"You Earned: Rs. ",N):n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement("div",{className:"top"},n.a.createElement("div",{className:"timer"},n.a.createElement(b,{setStop:x,questionNumber:u}))),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"bottm"},n.a.createElement(w,{data:[{id:1,question:"Which day is observed as World Standards Day?",answers:[{text:"Nov 15",correct:!1},{text:"Oct 14",correct:!0},{text:"Dec 2",correct:!1},{text:"June 26",correct:!1}]},{id:2,question:"What is celebrated on September 27 every year?",answers:[{text:"National Integration Day",correct:!1},{text:"Teachers' Day",correct:!1},{text:"International Literacy Day",correct:!1},{text:"World Tourism Day",correct:!0}]},{id:3,question:"How many miles is the Sun approximately away from the Earth?",answers:[{text:"93 million",correct:!0},{text:"9.3 million",correct:!1},{text:"193 million",correct:!1},{text:"39 million",correct:!1}]},{id:4,question:"Since 2002, what is the currency of Greece?",answers:[{text:"Drachma",correct:!1},{text:"Peso",correct:!1},{text:"Euro",correct:!0},{text:"Lira",correct:!1}]},{id:5,question:"Which ship was not a part of Christopher Columbus's first voyage in 1492?",answers:[{text:"Santa Maria",correct:!1},{text:"Nina",correct:!1},{text:"La Gorda",correct:!0},{text:"Pinta",correct:!1}]},{id:6,question:"How many states of U.S.A are not attached to the mainland?",answers:[{text:"2",correct:!0},{text:"1",correct:!1},{text:"4",correct:!1},{text:"3",correct:!1}]},{id:7,question:"Pakistan's Nuclear Plant is located in",answers:[{text:"Kahuta",correct:!0},{text:"Rawalpindi",correct:!1},{text:"Lahore",correct:!1},{text:"None of these",correct:!1}]},{id:8,question:"Which country does not have a monarch?",answers:[{text:"Britain",correct:!1},{text:"Japan",correct:!1},{text:"Afghanistan",correct:!0},{text:"Bhutan",correct:!1}]},{id:9,question:"The term 'computer bug' was inspired from a",answers:[{text:"Fly",correct:!1},{text:"Roach",correct:!1},{text:"Japanese Beetle",correct:!1},{text:"Moth",correct:!0}]},{id:10,question:"Which of the following scientists does not have a chemical name after him?",answers:[{text:"Enrico Fermi",correct:!1},{text:"Isaac Newton",correct:!0},{text:"Albert Einstein",correct:!1},{text:"Niels Bohr",correct:!1}]},{id:11,question:"Which African country was the first to get Independence?",answers:[{text:"Ghana",correct:!0},{text:"Nigeria",correct:!1},{text:"Zimbabwe",correct:!1},{text:"Congo",correct:!1}]},{id:12,question:"The currency of Hong Kong is",answers:[{text:"H. Dollar",correct:!0},{text:"H. Pound",correct:!1},{text:"Rouble",correct:!1},{text:"Dinar",correct:!1}]},{id:13,question:"Which country was elected out of the European Union?",answers:[{text:"Germany",correct:!1},{text:"France",correct:!1},{text:"Norway",correct:!0},{text:"Belgium",correct:!1}]},{id:14,question:"Space shuttle named 'Atlantis' was launched by",answers:[{text:"America",correct:!0},{text:"Britain",correct:!1},{text:"Australia",correct:!1},{text:"India",correct:!1}]}],setStop:x,questionNumber:u,setQuestionNumber:m,setEarned:v})))),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"pyramid"},n.a.createElement("ul",{className:"moneyList"},y.map(function(e){return n.a.createElement("li",{className:e.id===u?"moneyListItem active":"moneyListItem"},n.a.createElement("span",{className:"moneyListItemNumber"},e.id),n.a.createElement("span",{className:"moneyListItemAmount"},"Rs. ",e.amount))})))):n.a.createElement(h,{setUserName:c}))},E=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&a.e(1).then(a.bind(null,277)).then(function(t){var a=t.getCLS,r=t.getFID,n=t.getFCP,c=t.getLCP,o=t.getTTFB;a(e),r(e),n(e),c(e),o(e)})};o.a.createRoot(document.getElementById("root")).render(n.a.createElement(n.a.StrictMode,null,n.a.createElement(p,null))),E()},52:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/src_sounds_play.3d8ba0a6.mp3"},53:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/src_sounds_correct.d27f45ad.mp3"},56:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(275)},63:function(e,t,a){},65:function(e,t,a){}},[[56,4,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.045f0fdc.chunk.js.map